Guide to the YMCA - Student Division Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence of Student Division Secretaries, 1916-1943; Series I
  - Correspondence of A. R. Elliott
    - Douds, Charles T., 1929 -1931 (Box 20, Folder 278-279)
    - Ea-Ed (Box 20, Folder 280)
    - El-Ew (Box 20, Folder 281)
    - Easton, William B., 1931-1940 (Box 20, Folder 282-283)
    - Eddy, G. Sherwood, 1933-1937 (Box 20, Folder 284)
    - Eichelberger, Leslie, 1929-1933 (Box 20, Folder 285-286)
    - Elliott, A.J., 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 287-292)
    - Elliott, A.J., 1932-1935 (Box 21, Folder 293-300)
    - Espy, R.H. Edwin, 1935-1943 (Box 21, Folder 301)
    - Fa-Fe (Box 21, Folder 302)
    - Fi-F1 (Box 21, Folder 303)
    - Fo (Box 21, Folder 304)
    - Fr-Fu (Box 21, Folder 305)
    - Form correspondence, 1931-1936 (Box 22, Folder 306-315)
    - Form correspondence, 1936-1939 (Box 23, Folder 316-326)
    - Form correspondence, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 327-334)
    - Fox, Frederick S., Jr., 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 335)
    - Ga (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - Ge-Gl (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - Go-Gu (Box 24, Folder 338)
    - Garner, Ralph, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    - Goodwin, Loran E., 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - Graham, Thomas W., 1930-1932 (Box 25, Folder 341)
    - Groth, Wendell, 1930-1935 (Box 25, Folder 342)
    - Had-Han (Box 25, Folder 343)
    - Har-Hay (Box 25, Folder 344)
    - He-Hi (Box 25, Folder 345)
    - Ho (Box 25, Folder 346)
    - Hs-Hu (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - Hamilton, Grace Towns, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 348)
    - Hansen, Fred M., 1928-1939 (Box 25, Folder 349)
    - Hardwick, James T., 1931-1935 (Box 25, Folder 350)
    - Harner, Guy, 1931-1940 (Box 25, Folder 351)
    - Harrington, Elizabeth, 1934-1938 (Box 25, Folder 352)
    - Hayes, Egbert M., 1929-1932 (Box 25, Folder 353)
    - Hazen Foundation, 1931-1935 (Box 25, Folder 354)
    - Hearne, E.W., 1929-1932 (Box 25, Folder 355)
    - Heinsman, Harry L., 1928-1935 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    - Henry, John H., 1930-1933 (Box 25, Folder 357)
    - Henson, Francis A., 1931-1940 (Box 26, Folder 358-360)
    - Herschleb, Charles A., 1931-1934 (Box 26, Folder 361)
    - Hoisington, Homer L., 1928-1932 (Box 26, Folder 362)
    - Hollinger, Ralph, 1929-1930 (Box 26, Folder 363-364)
    - Hoover, Lyman, 1929-1940 (Box 26, Folder 365-366)
    - Home, H.H., 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 357)
    - House, Francis H., 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - Hulac, Charles, 1936-1940 (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - I (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - Ingalls, Harold B., 1929-1939 (Box 26, Folder 371-375)
    - Irving, George, 1931-1937 (Box 27, Folder 376-377)
    - Ja-Je (Box 27, Folder 378)
    - Jo (Box 27, Folder 379)
    - Johnson, Edwin C., 1934-1936 (Box 27, Folder 380)
    - Johnson, Robert C., 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 381)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1931-1935 (Box 27, Folder 382-385)
    - Johnston, O.T., 1936-1940 (Box 81, Folder 1068-1071)
    - Ka-Ke (Box 81, Folder 1072)
    - Ki (Box 81, Folder 1073)
    - Kl-Ku (Box 81, Folder 1074)
    - Kiang Wen Han, 1935-1940 (Box 27, Folder 388-389)
    - King, Herbert, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 390)
    - King, Herbert, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 391-392)
    - King, R.H., 1927-1932 (Box 28, Folder 393-394)
    - Kitchen, Wilmer J., 1929-1935 (Box 28, Folder 395-403)
    - Kitchen, Wilmer J., 1936 Jan-1938 (Box 29, Folder 404-407)
    - Koo, T.Z., 1931-1940 (Box 81, Folder 1075-1081)
    - La (Box 81, Folder 1082)
    - Le (Box 81, Folder 1083)
    - Li (Box 81, Folder 1084)
    - Lo-Ly (Box 81, Folder 1085)
    - Landram, Hugh, 1929-1934 (Box 29, Folder 408-409)
    - Landram, Hugh, 1935-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1086)
    - Little, Josephine, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 410)
    - Loomis, C.B., 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 411)
    - Ma (Box 82, Folder 1087)
    - Mc (Box 82, Folder 1088)
    - Me (Box 82, Folder 1089)
    - Mi-Mo (Box 82, Folder 1090)
    - Mu (Box 82, Folder 1091)
    - McConnell, J.J., Jr., 1931-1937 (Box 82, Folder 1092)
    - McCorkel, Roy, 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 413)
    - McKee, R.S., 1931-1936 (Box 82, Folder 1093-1096)
    - McKee, William, 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 414)
    - Mackie, Robert C., 1935-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1098-1101)
    - Mackie, Robert C., 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1102-1104)
    - McMichael, Jack R., Jr., 1937-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1097)
    - Magill, Orrin R., 1928-1936 Jun (Box 29, Folder 415-420)
    - Magill, Orrin R., 1936 Jul-Dec (Box 30, Folder 421-422)
    - Magill, Orrin R., 1937-1940 (Box 83, Folder 1105)
    - Manley, John E., 1931-1940 (Box 83, Folder 1106-1112)
    - Markely, Mary E., 1938-1940 (Box 83, Folder 1113)
    - Maydole, Hugh D., 1929-1932 (Box 30, Folder 423)
    - Mendenhall, W.O., 1934-1939 (Box 83, Folder 1114)
    - Messner, Sherwood, 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1932-1940 (Box 83, Folder 1115)
    - Miscellaneous financial solicitation correspondence, 1928-1935 (Box 30, Folder 425)
    - Moon, Carroll M., 1939 (Box 30, Folder 426)
    - Moss, Leslie B., 1933-1935 (Box 83, Folder 1116)
    - Mott, John R., 1935-1940, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 1117-1118)
    - Musselman, Charles A., 1928-1932 (Box 30, Folder 427)
    - Na (Box 84, Folder 1119)
    - Ne (Box 84, Folder 1120)
    - Ni-Ny (Box 84, Folder 1121)
    - Nelson, Claud D., 1929-1934 (Box 30, Folder 428-432)
    - Nelson, Claud D., 1935-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1122)
    - Nestingen, Edward L., 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1123)
    - O (Box 84, Folder 1124)
    - Oaten, BeverIy, 1934-1935 (Box 31, Folder 433)
    - Oaten, Beverly, 1936-1938 (Box 84, Folder 1125)
    - Pa (Box 84, Folder 1126)
    - Pe (Box 84, Folder 1127)
    - Ph-Pl (Box 84, Folder 1128)
    - Po-Q (Box 84, Folder 1129)
    - Pence, Owen E., 1935-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1130)
    - Porter, David R., 1931 Jan-1933 May (Box 84, Folder 1131-1137)
    - Porter, David R., 1933 Jun-1940 (Box 85, Folder 1138-1152)
    - Poulson, Harper W., 1940 (Box 85, Folder 1153)
    - Ra-Re (Box 85, Folder 1154)
    - Rh-Ri (Box 85, Folder 1155)
    - Rob-Roo (Box 85, Folder 1156)
    - Rop-Roy (Box 86, Folder 1157)
    - Ru (Box 86, Folder 1158)
    - Ramsey, Fred W., 1931-1935 (Box 86, Folder 1159)
    - Reque, Dikka, 1931-1932 (Box 86, Folder 1160)
    - Rhodes, Ivan B., 1929-1939 (Box 31, Folder 435)
    - Robertson, W. Spencer, 1933-1940 (Box 86, Folder 1161)
    - Roos, S., 1933-1937 (Box 86, Folder 1162)
    - Sa (Box 86, Folder 1163)
    - Sc (Box 86, Folder 1164)
    - Se (Box 86, Folder 1165)
    - Sh (Box 86, Folder 1166)
    - Si-Sl (Box 86, Folder 1167)
    - Sm-Sn (Box 86, Folder 1168)
    - Sp (Box 86, Folder 1169)
    - Sta-Sti (Box 86, Folder 1170)
    - Sto-Sw (Box 86, Folder 1171)
    - Schneider, Genevieve, 1933-1940 (Box 31, Folder 445)
    - Schram, William G., 1933-1935 (Box 31, Folder 446)
    - Schwieso, Charles, 1934-1939 (Box 31, Folder 447)
    - Scurlock, Stella, 1936-1938 (Box 31, Folder 448)
    - Shedd, Clarence P., 1931-1935 May (Box 31, Folder 449-451)
    - Shedd, Clarence P., 1935 Jun-1940 (Box 32, Folder 452-455)
    - Shelton, M.R., 1930-1932 (Box 86, Folder 1172)
    - Shultz, E.B. (see also: Series IV Central Region), 1933-1939 (Box 32, Folder 456)
    - Speers, William E., 1934-1940 (Box 32, Folder 457)
    - Stewart, George, 1933-1940 (Box 32, Folder 458-459)
    - Student Volunteer Movement, 1931-1937 (Box 86, Folder 1173)
    - Sweet, William E., 1933-1940 (Box 32, Folder 460)
    - Sweetman, H. Ray, 1928-1932 (Box 32, Folder 461)
    - Sweetman, H. Ray, 1933 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Ta-Th (Box 32, Folder 462)
    - Ti-Tu (Box 32, Folder 463)
    - Taylor, Harry B., 1933-1935 (Box 32, Folder 464)
    - Thompson, Hugo, 1935-1938 (Box 32, Folder 465-469)
    - Tinker, Wellington H., 1931-1936 (Box 33, Folder 470)
    - Tobias, Channing H., 1929-1940 (Box 33, Folder 471)
    - Tompkins, Leslie J., 1937-1940 (Box 33, Folder 472)
    - Treasurer's office, 1931-1938 (Box 33, Folder 473-475)
    - Tucker, Luther, 1933-1940 (Box 33, Folder 476-480)
    - U (Box 33, Folder 481)
    - Uphaus, Willard, 1931-1940 (Box 33, Folder 482-484)
    - V (Box 34, Folder 485)
    - VanDusen, Henry P., 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 486-492)
    - Visser 't Hooft, Willem, 1931-1932 (Box 86, Folder 1174)
    - Visser 't Hooft, Willem, 1933-1940 (Box 34, Folder 493-496)
    - Wa (Box 35, Folder 497)
    - We-Wh (Box 35, Folder 498)
    - Wic-Wig (Box 35, Folder 499)
    - Wil (Box 35, Folder 500)
    - Win-Wu (Box 35, Folder 501)
    - Wiley, S. Wirt, 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 502)
    - Williams, Chester, 1931-1936 (Box 35, Folder 503)
    - Williams, Urban, 1928-1939 (Box 35, Folder 504-505)
    - Willits, Howard D., 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 506)
    - Wilson, Frank T., 1929-1936 (Box 35, Folder 507-509)
    - Wilson, Lucian C., 1930-1939 (Box 35, Folder 510-513)
    - Wilson, Robert S., 1928-1929 (Box 36, Folder 514)
    - Workman, George B., 1929-1934 (Box 36, Folder 515-516)
    - Y (Box 36, Folder 517)
    - Yard, Molly, 1938-1940 (Box 36, Folder 518)
    - Yarrow, E.A. (see also:Hazen Foundation), 1933-1938 (Box 36, Folder 519)
    - Yergan, Max, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 520)
    - Young, William L., 1933-1935 (Box 36, Folder 521)
    - YWCA Natlonal Board, 1931-1940 (Box 36, Folder 522-525)
    - YWCA National Board - Helen Morton, 1934-1936 Jun (Box 36, Folder 526-528)
    - YWCA National Board - Helen Morton, 1936 Jul-1940 Mar (Box 37, Folder 529-533)
    - YWCA National Board, 1940 Apr-Dec (Box 37, Folder 534)
    - Z (Box 37, Folder 535)
    - Zahn, Susan, 1931-1940 (Box 37, Folder 536-538)
  - Correspondence of Other Secretaries and Staff
    - Miscellaneous, 1922-1937 (Box 38, Folder 539)
    - Brown, Forrest D. with various individuals (Box 38, Folder 540)
    - Colvin, Harold with Charles Schwieso, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 541)
    - Henson, Francis with various individuals (Box 38, Folder 542)
    - Ingalls, Harold with various individuals, A-K (Box 38, Folder 543)
    - Ingalls, Harold with various individuals, L-R (Box 38, Folder 544)
    - Ingalls, Harold with various individuals, S-W (Box 38, Folder 545)
    - Mendenhall, W.W. with E.B. Schultz, 1929-1930 (Box 38, Folder 546)
    - VanDusen, Henry P. with B.G. Alexander, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 547)
    - VanDusen' Henry P. with E.W. Brandenburg, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 548)
    - VanDusen, Henry P. with F.M. Hansen, E.W. Hearne, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 549)
    - VanDusen, Henry P. with R.H. King, K.Kline, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 550)
    - VanDusen, Henry P. with W.W. Mendenhall, C.A. Tevebaugh, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 551)
    - VanDusen, Henry P. with F.H. West, U. Williams, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 552)
    - Wilson, Frank T. with Wilmer Kitchen, 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 553)
    - Wilson, L.C. with various individuals, C-H (Box 38, Folder 554)
    - Wilson, Frank T. with Claud D. Nelson, 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 555)
    - Wilson, Frank T. with H.B. Taylor, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 556)
    - Wilson, L.C. with Wilmer Kitchen, 1928-1931 (Box 38, Folder 557)
    - Wilson, L.C. with Leo Kohl, 1928-1929 (Box 38, Folder 558)
    - Wilson, L.C. with Leo Kohl, 1930-1932 (Box 38, Folder 559)
    - Wilson, L.C. with L.A. Pickett, 1928-1930 (Box 38, Folder 560)
    - Wilson, L.C. with H.R. Sweetman, 1928-1932 (Box 38, Folder 561)
    - Wilson, L.C. and U. Williams, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 562)
- National Committees, Commissions, Councils, 1899-1958; Series II
  These administrative bodies are listed in alphabetical order by their official name. Name changes over time and the interrelationships between the various bodies are left for the researcher to determine, with the help of the lists provided in the Introduction. Subheadings delineate the various activities of the administrative bodies.
  - Advance Program Commission of the Student YMCA
    - Minutes, reports, correspondence, 1923,n.d. (Box 39, Folder 563)
    - Minutes, reports, correspondence, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 564)
    - Minutes, reports, 1925-1926 (Box 39, Folder 565)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1923,n.d. (Box 39, Folder 566)
    - Committee on Relationships, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 567)
    - Regarding study produced by Commission, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 568)
    - Surveys of regional and local work, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 569)
    - Survey of regional and local work, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 570)
    - Survey of regional and local work, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 571)
    - Subcommittee II, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 572)
    - Subcommittee III, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 573)
    - Subcommittee IV, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 574)
    - Subcommittee IV, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 575)
    - Subcommittee IV, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 576)
    - Subcommittee IV, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 577)
    - Subcommittee IV, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 578)
    - Subcommittee V, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 579)
    - Subcommittee VI, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 580)
    - Subcommittee VII, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 581)
    - Subcommittee VIII, 1923-1925 (Box 40, Folder 582)
    - Subcommittee IX, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 583)
    - Subcommittee X, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 584)
    - Subcommittee XI, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 585)
  - Council of Christian Associations
    - Christian World Education Committee, 1927- 1930 (Box 40, Folder 586)
    - Commission on the Message of the Movements, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 587)
    - Commission on the Place and Function of the Student Christian Associations, c.1929 (Box 40, Folder 588)
    - Economics Commission, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 589)
    - Economics Commission, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 590)
    - Economics Commission, 1932-1933 (Box 41, Folder 591)
    - Miscellaneous, 1923-1929 (Box 41, Folder 592)
  - Council of North American Student Movements
    - Miscellaneous, 1923-1929 (Box 41, Folder 593)
  - International Committee of the YMCAs
    - General, 1916-1923 (Box 41, Folder 594)
    - Student Department - Correspondence of Hans P. Anderson re: the General Secretaryship, 1899-1900 (Box 41, Folder 595)
    - Evangelism Commission, 1915-1921 (Box 41, Folder 596)
    - Student Department - Form letters, forms, 1915-1925 (Box 41, Folder 597)
    - Student Department - Miscellaneous, 1899-1915 (Box 41, Folder 598)
    - Student Department - Miscellaneous, 1916-1920,n.d. (Box 41, Folder 599)
    - Student Department - Reports, 1901-1904 (Box 41, Folder 600)
    - Student Department - Reports, 1908-1909 (Box 41, Folder 601)
    - Student Department - Reports, 1915-1919 (Box 41, Folder 602)
    - Student Department - Reports, 1918-1927 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1904-1906 (Box 41, Folder 603)
    - Conference of International and State Student Secretaries and of Secretaries of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions, Nashville, TN, 1905 Oct (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1907-1908 (Box 41, Folder 604)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 605)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 606)
    - Student Department - Secretariest Conferences, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 607)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 608)
    - Student Department - Secretaries' Conferences, 1917,1925 (Box 42, Folder 609)
    - Theological section of the Student Department, 1916,1917 (Box 42, Folder 610)
  - National Board of the YMCA
    - Financial reports of Student Division, 1928-1954 (Box 42, Folder 611)
    - Regarding professional preparation, 1953-1958 (Box 42, Folder 612)
    - Special Committee on Student Work, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 613)
  - National Council of Student Associations /National Council of Student Christian Associations
    - Ad Interim Committee, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 614)
    - Commission on Leadership, 1929-1930 (Box 42, Folder 615)
    - Commission on Leadership, 1931,n.d. (Box 42, Folder 616)
    - Minutes, reports, 1925-1927 (Box 42, Folder 617)
    - Committee on Program Emphases, 1929,1930 (Box 42, Folder 618)
    - Minutes, reports, 1928-1930 (Box 42, Folder 619)
    - Minutes, reports, 1931-1933,n.d. (Box 42, Folder 620)
    - Administrative Committee, 1934-1941 (Box 43, Folder 621)
    - Administrative Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 622)
    - National Council of Student Christian Associations minutes, actions, war-work, 1943 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Committee, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 623)
    - Minutes, reports, 1933-1944 (Box 43, Folder 624)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934-1949,n.d. (Box 43, Folder 625)
    - Personnel Committee, 1939-1944 (Box 43, Folder 626)
    - Publicity Material, 1933-1934,n.d. (Box 43, Folder 627)
    - Study Committee, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 628)
    - Minutes, 1922-1924 (Box 43, Folder 629)
    - Commission on General Agencies, 1933 (Box 43, Folder 630)
    - Commission on Student Work, 1934,1941 (Box 43, Folder 631)
    - Commission on Student Work, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 632)
    - Conference on the Association Profession, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 633)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, 1926,1931-1947 (Box 44, Folder 634)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926,1943-1945,n.d. (Box 44, Folder 635)
    - Public Relations Office, 1940-1943,1950 (Box 44, Folder 636)
    - Student Department Committee, 1924-1927 (Box 44, Folder 637)
    - Student Division reports, 1927,1929, 1930,1943 (Box 44, Folder 638)
    - Student secretaries' reports, 1926-1928 (Box 44, Folder 639)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council
    See also NICC material in Series VII, Addendum - 2010
    - Administrative Committee, 1935-1937 (Box 44, Folder 640)
    - Administrative Committee, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 641)
    - Administrative Committee, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 642)
    - Administrative Committee, 1940-1943 (Box 44, Folder 643)
    - Administrative Committee, 1944-1946 (Box 44, Folder 644)
    - Administrative Committee, 1947- 1948 (Box 44, Folder 645)
    - Administrative Committee, 1950-1951,n.d. (Box 44, Folder 646)
    - Annual meeting, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 647)
    - Annual meeting, 1939,1940 (Box 45, Folder 648)
    - Annual meeting, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 649)
    - Annual meeting, 1942,1944 (Box 45, Folder 650)
    - Annual meeting, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 651)
    - Annual meeting, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 652)
    - Annual meeting, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 653)
    - Annual meeting, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 654)
    - Annual meeting, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 655)
    - Committee on Christian Faith and Heritage, 1941-1947 (Box 45, Folder 656)
    - Committee on Effective Citizenship, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 657)
    - Committee on Higher Education, 1944-1946 (Box 45, Folder 658)
    - Committee on Organization and Structure, 1949-1950 (Box 45, Folder 659)
    - Committee on Relations with the Churches, 1938-1945,n.d. (Box 45, Folder 660)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1937-1940 (Box 45, Folder 661)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1942-1951 (Box 45, Folder 662)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936-1941 (Box 46, Folder 663)
    - Miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box 46, Folder 664)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946-1948,n.d. (Box 46, Folder 665)
    - National Commission on Socio-Economic Education, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 666)
    - National Assembly Planning Committee, 1937-1946 (Box 46, Folder 667)
    - National Student Christian Consultation, Denison University, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 668)
    - Personnel Committee, 1936-1940 (Box 46, Folder 669)
    - Personnel Committee, 1941-1947 (Box 46, Folder 670)
    - Planning Committee, 1941-1951 (Box 46, Folder 671)
    - Program Commission - minutes, reports, 1939-1951 (Box 46, Folder 672)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, 1938-1944 (Box 46, Folder 673)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 674)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 675)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 676)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, 1949-1951 (Box 46, Folder 677)
    - Program Commission - resource materials, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 678)
    - Staff correspondence and directives, 1939-1946 (Box 47, Folder 679)
    - Staff correspondence and directives, 1947-1951 (Box 47, Folder 680)
    - Staff study program, 1941-1946 (Box 47, Folder 681)
    - Staff study program, 1947,n.d. (Box 47, Folder 682)
  - National Student Committee
    - Administrative Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 683)
    - Advisory Committee on the Development of Student YMCAs in Metropolitan Centers, c.1950 (Box 47, Folder 684)
    - Commission on Message and Mission, 1948-1950 (Box 47, Folder 685)
    - Commission on Religious Approach, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 686)
    - Committee on Reorganization, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder 687)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1928-1931 (Box 47, Folder 688)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1941-1952,n.d. (Box 47, Folder 689)
    - Executive Committee, 1933-1935 (Box 47, Folder 690)
    - Executive Committee, 1937-1953 (Box 47, Folder 691)
    - Minutes, 1927-1932 (Box 47, Folder 692)
    - Minutes, 1943-1946 (Box 47, Folder 693)
    - Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 48, Folder 694)
    - Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 48, Folder 695)
    - Reports, 1941-1951, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 696)
  - National Student Council of the YMCA
    - Administrative Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 48, Folder 697)
    - By-laws, 1944,1947,1959-1963 (Box 48, Folder 698)
    - Centennial Committee, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 699)
    - Committee on Participation of Men Students in Intercollegiate Activities, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 700)
    - Financial reports, 1954-1955 (Box 48, Folder 701)
    - Forward Program study, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 702)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 48, Folder 703)
    - Minutes, 1945-1951 (Box 48, Folder 704)
    - Miscellaneous, 1946-1949 (Box 48, Folder 705)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1953,n.d. (Box 48, Folder 706)
    - National Advisory Council, 1947-1951 (Box 48, Folder 707)
    - National Advisory Council, 1952-1955 (Box 48, Folder 708)
    - National Student Personnel Committee, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 709)
    - National Student Personnel Committee, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 710)
    - National Student Personnel Committee, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 711)
    - National Student Personnel Committee, 1948-1951 (Box 49, Folder 712)
    - Staff Correspondence, 1944-1952 (Box 49, Folder 713)
    - Flyers, 1951, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - National Student Council of the YMCA and YWCA
    - Administrative Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 49, Folder 714)
    - Administrative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 715)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1960,n.d. (Box 49, Folder 716)
    - National Student Assembly of the YMCA-YWCA, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 717)
    - Program Commission, 1951-1959 (Box 49, Folder 718)
    - Program materials, 1952,1956 (Box 49, Folder 719)
  - National Student Assembly of the YMCA-YWCA
    - Projects, 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 720)
    - Reports, 1951-1954 (Box 49, Folder 721)
    - Staff correspondence and directives, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 722)
  - Spiritual Emphasis Committee
    - Memoranda, reports, 1930, 1933,1934 (Box 50, Folder 723)
    - Minutes, 1931-1933 (Box 50, Folder 724)
    - Minutes, 1934 (Box 50, Folder 725)
    - Financial correspondence, 1931 (Box 50, Folder 726)
    - Financial correspondence, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 727)
    - Financial correspondence, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 728)
    - Financial reports, 1931-1933 (Box 50, Folder 729)
  - Student Christian Association Movement
    - Assembly, 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 730)
    - Assembly, 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 731)
    - Assembly, 1946-1947 (Box 50, Folder 732)
    - Assembly, 1950-1951,n.d. (Box 50, Folder 733)
  - Student Secretaries Association
    - Bulletins, memoranda, 1928-1952,n.d. (Box 50, Folder 734)
    - Intercollegian Program Service: A Program of Interracial Education, 1931-1932 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - SSA Bulletin, 1948 Feb (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence of H.L. Seamans, 1930-1933 (Box 50, Folder 735)